<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TDM</string>
    <string-array name="summary">
        <item>Design Patterns in Java gives you the hands-on practice and deep insight you need to fully leverage the significant power of design patterns in any Java software project. The perfect complement to the classic Design Patterns, this learn-by-doing workbook applies the latest Java features and best practices to all of the original 23 patterns identified in that groundbreaking text. Drawing on their extensive experience as Java instructors and programmers, Steve Metsker and Bill Wake illuminate each pattern with real Java programs, clear UML diagrams, and compelling exercises. You\'ll move quickly from theory to application―learning how to improve new code and refactor existing code for simplicity, manageability, and performance.</item>
        <item>System developers have used modeling languages for decades to specify, visualize, construct, and document systems. The Unified Modeling Language (UML) is one of those languages. UML makes it possible for team members to collaborate by providing a common language that applies to a multitude of different systems. Essentially, it enables you to communicate solutions in a consistent, tool-supported language.Today, UML has become the standard method for modeling software systems, which means you\'re probably confronting this rich and expressive language more than ever before. And even though you may not write UML diagrams yourself, you\'ll still need to interpret diagrams written by others.UML 2.0 in a Nutshell from O\'Reilly feels your pain. It\'s been crafted for professionals like you who must read, create, and understand system artifacts expressed using UML. Furthermore, it\'s been fully revised to cover version 2.0 of the language.This comprehensive new edition not only provides a quick-reference to all UML 2.0 diagram types, it also explains key concepts in a way that appeals to readers already familiar with UML or object-oriented programming concepts.</item>
        <item>Portable and precise, this pocket-sized guide delivers ready answers for the day-to-day administration of SQL Server. Zero in on core support and maintenance tasks using quick-reference tables, instructions, and lists. You\'ll get the focused information you need to save time and get the job done—whether at your desk or in the field!</item>
        <item>Author Jason Ostrander walks developers through the different choices available on their way to creating a well-designed application for Android. While building a simple application, Jason works through the basics of Android UI development including layout, event handling, menus and notifications. The author then shows the proper way to load and display images, create advanced dialogs and progress indicators, add animation, and how to build custom UI elements. Jason discusses the proper way of adding interaction through gestures and the advanced graphical options available using Canvas, Renderscript and OpenGL. Finally, he discusses tablet development, the unique differences between phone and tablet UI, and the new APIs available to tablet developers.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
